To expand internationally, firms use entry strategies like exporting, licensing, and contract manufacturing.
为了进行国际扩张，
企业会采用出口、
许可和合同制造等进入策略。
The choice of strategy is based on their goals, market conditions, and capabilities, each offering unique benefits and risks.
策略的选择取决于他们的目标、
市场条件和能力，
每种策略都具有独特的优势和风险。
An American clothing brand, EcoStyle, may enter foreign markets by exporting and selling its clothing line to buyers using domestic intermediaries.
美国服装品牌环保风尚（EcoStyle）
能够通过出口
并利用国内中间商销售其服装系列给买家
来进入国外市场。
This low-risk indirect exporting strategy allows the company to test the market with limited control over marketing activities.
这种低风险的间接出口策略
使得企业能够在对营销活动
控制有限的情况下测试市场。
Eventually, it could export directly to foreign markets, yielding higher profits and control over business operations.
最终，
它能够直接出口到国外市场，
从而获得更高的利润和对业务运营的控制。
But with higher investment and risk.
但是投资和风险会更高。
Alternatively, Ecostyle could license its brand to reputable retailers or manufacturers abroad, allowing them to sell the products on its behalf.
或者，
环保风尚能够将其品牌授权给
国外知名的零售商或制造商，
从而允许他们代表自己销售产品。
It can leverage the partners' market knowledge and distribution networks, minimizing financial risks.
它能够利用合作伙伴的市场知识
和分销网络来最大限度地降低财务风险。
Lastly, EcoStyle might opt for contract manufacturing by outsourcing production to manufacturers in cost-efficient regions.
最后，
环保风尚可能会选择合同制造，
从而将生产外包给
具有成本效益的地区的制造商。
This strategy enables it to scale production while reducing manufacturing costs and distribution complexities.
这一策略使其能够扩大生产规模，
同时降低制造成本
和分销的复杂性。
But, it increases risk due to less control over production.
但是，由于对生产的控制较少，
因此风险也会随之增加。